[
    {
        "front": "せいかつ",
        "back": "生活 \ndaily life",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "かつどう",
        "back": "活動 \nactivity",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "かっぱつ",
        "back": "活発 \nactive",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "まわる(intr.)",
        "back": "回る(intr.) \nto revolve",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "いつかい",
        "back": "1回 \none time",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "まわす(tr.)",
        "back": "回す(tr.) \nto revolve",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぜんかい",
        "back": "前回 \nthe last time",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "かいてんずし",
        "back": "回転寿司 \nsushi conveyor belt",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "おもに",
        "back": "主に \nmainly",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゅじん",
        "back": "主人 \nhusband",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゅしょく",
        "back": "主食 \nstaple food",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "おもな",
        "back": "主な \nmain",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "＊もちぬし",
        "back": "＊持ち主 \nowner",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "いろ",
        "back": "色 \ncolor",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "とくしょく",
        "back": "特色 \nspecial feature",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちゃいろ",
        "back": "茶色 \nbrown color",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "けしき",
        "back": "景色 \nscenery",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "いろいろ",
        "back": "色々 \nvarious",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "かたち",
        "back": "形 \nshape, form",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "ずけい",
        "back": "図形 \nfigure",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "にんぎょう",
        "back": "人形 \ndoll",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "せいほうけい",
        "back": "正方形 \nsquare shape",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "しな",
        "back": "品 \ngoods, products",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "しょうひん",
        "back": "商品 \ngoods, products",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "しなもの",
        "back": "品物 \ngoods",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "しょくりょうひん",
        "back": "食料品 \nfood items",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "でんきせいひん",
        "back": "電気製品 \nelectric products",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "さくひん",
        "back": "作品 \nmasterpiece",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "みんぞく",
        "back": "民族 \nrace, mankind",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "じゅうみん",
        "back": "住民 \nresident",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "みんしゅしゅぎ",
        "back": "民主主義 \ndemocracy",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふく",
        "back": "服 \nclothes",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "ようふく",
        "back": "洋服 \nwestern clothes",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "わふく",
        "back": "和服 \njapanese style clothes",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "せいふく",
        "back": "制服 \nuniform",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "いぬ",
        "back": "犬 \ndog",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "にほんけん",
        "back": "日本犬 \njapanese dog",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "こいぬ",
        "back": "子犬 \npuppy",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "おなじ",
        "back": "同じ \nsame",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "どうじに",
        "back": "同時に \nat the same time",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    },
    {
        "front": "どうきゅうせい",
        "back": "同級生 \nclassmate",
        "chapter": "N4 K13"
    }
]